Guide to the Jobs With Justice Photographs 1980-2012
Jobs With Justice Photographs
- Miscellaneous Photos -- 2001-2003 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Philly -- 4/4/2002-- D & A (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Boston (Box 93, Folder 6)
- KY-Sonora Delegation in Mexico (Box 93, Folder 7)
- KY-Sonora Delegation in Mexico (Box 93, Folder 8)
- KY-Sonora Delegation in Mexico (Box 93, Folder 9)
- KY-Sonora Delegation in Mexico (Box 93, Folder 10)
- KY-Sonora Delegation in Mexico (Box 93, Folder 11)
- KY-Sonora Exchange in Kentucky (Box 93, Folder 12)
- KY-Sonora Exchange in Kentucky (Box 93, Folder 13)
- KY-Sonora Exchange in Kentucky (Box 93, Folder 14)
- KY-Sonora Exchange in Kentucky (Box 93, Folder 15)
- KY-Sonora Exchange in Kentucky (Box 93, Folder 16)
- KY-Sonora Exchange in Kentucky (Box 93, Folder 17)
- Miami - Mt. Sinai (Box 93, Folder 18)
- Miami - Mt. Sinai (Box 93, Folder 19)
- 4/4/2002 Atlanta (Box 93, Folder 20)
- 4/4/2002 Atlanta (Box 93, Folder 21)
- Philly Temple -- 4/4/2002 (Box 93, Folder 22)
- Philly Temple -- 4/4/2002 (Box 93, Folder 23)
- Quebec FTAA (Box 93, Folder 24)
- Quebec FTAA (Box 93, Folder 25)
- NYC WFF (Box 93, Folder 26)
- NYC WFF (Box 93, Folder 27)
- NYC WFF (Box 93, Folder 28)
- WSF (Box 93, Folder 29)
- WSF (Box 93, Folder 30)
- WSF (Box 93, Folder 31)
- Quebec FTAA (Box 93, Folder 32)
- Quebec to DC IMF Protest (Box 93, Folder 33)
- Quebec to DC IMF Protest (Box 93, Folder 34)
- Quebec to DC IMF Protest (Box 93, Folder 35)
- Seattle/King County Building and Construction Trades Council, AFL-CIO -- 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Seattle/King County Building and Construction Trades Council, AFL-CIO -- 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Solidarity School -- 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Jobs with Justice - Miscellaneous photos -- 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Jobs with Justice - Miscellaneous photos -- 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Jobs with Justice - Rally photos, 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Jobs with Justice - Rallies, 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 7)
- Jobs with Justice -- Rallies, 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 8)
- Jobs with Justice -- Rallies, 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 9)
- Jobs with Justice -- Rallies, 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 10)
- Jobs with Justice -- Rallies, 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 11)
- Jobs with Justice -- Rallies, 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 12)
- Jobs with Justice -- Rallies, 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 13)
- Jobs with Justice -- Fall 1990 (Box 94, Folder 14)
- Jobs with Justice -- Fall 1990 (Box 94, Folder 15)
- Jobs with Justice - CWA rally (Box 94, Folder 16)
- Jobs with Justice - Rallies, 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 17)
- Jobs with Justice -- Rallies, 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 18)
- Jobs with Justice -- Rallies, 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 19)
- Jobs with Justice -- Rallies, 1980-1999 (Box 94, Folder 20)
- Fred Azcarate (1997) (Box 94, Folder 21)
- Jobs with Justice -- Miscellaneous (Box 94, Folder 22)
- San Antonio Old (Box 94, Folder 23)
- Old Florida (Box 94, Folder 24)
- Old Florida (Box 94, Folder 25)
- Old Florida (Box 94, Folder 26)
- Old Florida (Box 94, Folder 27)
- Old Florida (Box 94, Folder 28)
- Old Florida (Box 94, Folder 29)
- Jobs with Justice - Miscellaneous Photos, 1990-1999 (Box 94, Folder 30)
- Tulsa, OK (Box 94, Folder 31)
- Chicago Photos - late 1990s, 1990-1999 (Box 94, Folder 32)
- Huntington, WV Rally -- "Healthcare For All" (Box 94, Folder 33)
- OSU CWA, 1990 (Box 94, Folder 34)
- OSU CWA, 1990 (Box 94, Folder 35)
- Phoenix Action & Tucson (Box 94, Folder 36)
- Jobs with Justice -- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 94, Folder 37)
- Cleveland Action (Box 94, Folder 38)
- Jobs with Justice -- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 94, Folder 39)
- Old -- MO (Box 94, Folder 40)
- Pittsburgh Annual Meeting (Box 94, Folder 41)
- Jobs with Justice - Buffalo (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Old DC (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Old Texas (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Old Atlanta JwJ Photos - Newt Gingrich photos by Cindy Lucas (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Old Atlanta JwJ Photos - Newt Gingrich photos by Cindy Lucas (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Old Atlanta JwJ Photos - Newt Gingrich photos by Cindy Lucas (Box 95, Folder 6)
- National DOA Against Corporate Greed (Box 95, Folder 7)
- National DOA Against Corporate Greed (Box 95, Folder 8)
- National DOA Against Corporate Greed (Box 95, Folder 9)
- National DOA Against Corporate Greed (Box 95, Folder 10)
- National DOA Against Corporate Greed (Box 95, Folder 11)
- National DOA Against Corporate Greed (Box 95, Folder 12)
- National DOA Against Corporate Greed (Box 95, Folder 13)
- National DOA Against Corporate Greed (Box 95, Folder 14)
- WRB Hearing -- 6/24/1999 (Box 95, Folder 15)
- WRB Hearing 6/24/1999 (Box 95, Folder 16)
- Overnite Atlanta (Box 95, Folder 17)
- Grinch of the Year Party (Box 95, Folder 18)
- ATL Grady Hospital (Box 95, Folder 19)
- Jobs with Justice - Miscellaneous Photos (Box 95, Folder 20)
- Texas - 12/10 (either 1991 or 1997) (Box 95, Folder 21)
- Portland (Box 95, Folder 22)
- Jobs with Justice - Miscellaneous Photos (Box 95, Folder 23)
- PDX Students - @ late 1990's - Jerry Atkins (Box 95, Folder 24)
- Jobs with Justice - Miscellaneous Photos 1987-1997 (Box 95, Folder 25)
- Jobs with Justice - Miscellaneous Photos 1987-1997 (Box 95, Folder 26)
- Jobs with Justice - Miscellaneous Photos 1987-1997 (Box 95, Folder 27)
- Jobs with Justice - Miscellaneous Photos 1987-1997 (Box 95, Folder 28)
- Jobs with Justice - Miscellaneous Photos 1987-1997 (Box 95, Folder 29)
- Jobs with Justice - Miscellaneous Photos 1987-1997 (Box 95, Folder 30)
- Chicago Conference 1997? (Box 95, Folder 31)
- Pittsburgh Annual Meeting (Box 95, Folder 32)
- Pittsburgh Annual Meeting (Box 95, Folder 33)
- Pittsburgh Annual Meeting (Box 95, Folder 34)
- Pittsburgh Annual Meeting (Box 95, Folder 35)
- Pittsburgh Annual Meeting (Box 95, Folder 36)
- 1990's Welfare Reform (Box 95, Folder 37)
- Missouri DIO Hearing (year?) (Box 95, Folder 38)
- Late 1990's Workfare DOA (Box 95, Folder 39)
- STL living wage 2000 (Box 95, Folder 40)
- Annual Meeting 1999 (Box 95, Folder 41)
- Annual meeting 1999 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Annual meeting 1998-1999 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Conference (Box 96, Folder 3)
- President's Meeting ? (year? Late 90's?) (Box 96, Folder 4)
- 1998 Michael Moore "The Big One" Benefit (Boston?) (Box 96, Folder 5)
- 1998 Michael Moore "The Big One" Benefit (Boston?) (Box 96, Folder 6)
- Atlanta JwJ (Box 96, Folder 7)
- Jobs with Justice - Misc. (Box 96, Folder 8)
- CEJ Buffalo -- 1990's, 1990-1999 (Box 96, Folder 9)
- Jobs with Justice - Misc. Rally Photos (Box 96, Folder 10)
- Jobs with Justice -- Misc. Rally Photos (Box 96, Folder 11)
- Jobs with Justice -- Misc. Rally Photos (Box 96, Folder 12)
- Jobs with Justice -- Misc. Rally Photos (Box 96, Folder 13)
- Jobs with Justice -- Misc. Rally Photos (Box 96, Folder 14)
- Jobs with Justice -- Misc. Rally Photos (Box 96, Folder 15)
- Jobs with Justice -- Misc. Rally Photos (Box 96, Folder 16)
- Jobs with Justice -- Misc. Rally Photos (Box 96, Folder 17)
- Jobs with Justice - Misc. Mat'l. that was mixed in w/photos (Box 96, Folder 18)
- Atlanta (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Jobs with Justice - Cleveland, OH (Box 97, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Jobs with Justice - Louisville, Kentucky (Box 97, Folder 4)
- JwJ - Misc. (Box 97, Folder 5)
- DC Press Briefing "Working Hard" Release -- Dec. 8, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- DC Welfare day of Action (Box 97, Folder 7)
- DC Action for ABC Lockout (Box 97, Folder 8)
- DC Action for ABC Lockout (Box 97, Folder 9)
- DC Action for ABC Lockout (Box 97, Folder 10)
- Highlander Training -- Fundraising Training other DC stuff (Box 97, Folder 11)
- Arkansas AFL-CIO -- Little Rock, Ark. (Box 97, Folder 12)
- JwJ Portland OR (Box 97, Folder 13)
- City - Fred Azcarate (Box 97, Folder 14)
- JwJ -- Misc. (Box 97, Folder 15)
- JwJ -- Misc. larger photos (Box 97, Folder 16)
- JwJ - Teamsters (Box 97, Folder 17)
  photo mounted for an exhibit
- PACE Local 5243 (Box 97, Folder 18)
- Higher Ed. -- Rally (Box 97, Folder 19)
- Cleveland Workers (Box 97, Folder 20)
- UT Students (Box 97, Folder 21)
- JwJ - Faculty Support Living Wage (Box 97, Folder 22)
- JwJ Rally (Box 97, Folder 23)
- UNITE! Rally (Box 97, Folder 24)
- PLASC & JwJ - Cross - Border Organizing for Workers' Rights (Box 97, Folder 25)
- Our Lady of Victory Hospital (Box 97, Folder 26)
- Trabajos Justicia (Box 97, Folder 27)
- Cleveland needs a living wage (Box 97, Folder 28)
- St. Louis jobs and Living Wage Campaign (Box 97, Folder 29)
- Stop Corporate Greed (Box 97, Folder 30)
- JwJ - Misc. (Box 97, Folder 31)
- The Lantern - 2000 - May 12 (Box 97, Folder 32)
- Denver Post - Article on Janitors (Box 97, Folder 33)
- JwJ -- Misc. (Box 97, Folder 34)
- Herald-Sun, Durham, South Carolina - Anti-Sweatshop Law (Box 97, Folder 35)
- Louisville Eccentric Observer -- 2/24/1999 (Box 97, Folder 36)
- JwJ -- Misc. (Box 97, Folder 37)
- JwJ -- Misc. (Box 97, Folder 38)
- Wobbly Walk Through the Siskiyous (Box 98, Folder 1)
- JwJ - Larger photos mounted for exhibits (Box 99, Folder 1)
  One photo is mounted on construction paper.